# **Lucas Portet**

lucasportet@gmail.com
+336-789-945-75
lucasportet.com

# **Summary**

I'm Lucas, a full-stack developer focused on making meaningful interfaces and experiences. Working at the crossroad of technology, design and business, I like to see my role as the bridge between the chaos of the machine and human language.

### **Education**

#### **Epitech**

MS Computer science (2017 - 2022)
Concentration in web applications, interactions and low-level technologies.

#### **EF San Francisco**

Intensive english course (summer 2016)

# **Experience**

SII - Full stack developer (July 2018 to Dec 2018)

Built a visual dashboard for scrum teams. Agile project management. Used Vue, Node, Express and Mongo. Internship.

Gang of pizza - Community manager (2016 to 2018)

Managed the digital presence of the company. Targeted ad campaigns. Creation of social media graphics.

**PAC Pizza Chef School** - Assistant trainer (2016 & 2018 summers) Pizza ATM training course in Cincinnati (2016) and Toronto (2018).

## Skills

Languages	Frameworks	Tools	Design
Javascript	Vue	Git	Adobe Suite
Python	React	Scrum	Sketch
C++	Node	Mongo	UX research
Swift	Express	Webpack	Design thinking

# Languages

French	English	Spanish	
Native	Professional	Notions	

## Misc

Born	Live in	<b>Driving license</b>	Personality
15/06/1999	Rennes, FR	Yes	ENTP-A